gemioli.com 2019-12-02

# Gemioli | Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction

We at Gemioli (“we”, “us”, “our”) care about your privacy very seriously and we do our best to protect your privacy and keep your information secure.

This Privacy Policy describes what information we are collecting at our Services (Gemioli website and games located at [https://gemioli.com](https://gemioli.com/), including apps and games available on social media/networks and on mobile app stores) and what we’re doing with it, and your rights related to the processing of such Personal Data you’ll be entitle to.

By using our Services, you agree and accept this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. In the future our Services may change and we reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes if appropriate. So new versions will be here and we encourage you to check this page regularly so that you know our current practices.

If you are based in Europe for the purposes of Europe’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the Data Controller of your personal information is Dmitriy Kapustin having its office at Okrujnoe sh. 32-102, Vologda, Russia.

### 2\. What Information We Collect and How We Use it

When you use our Services, we may collect Personal Data from you in two ways – information that you provide and information we automatically collect.

Usually you send us personally identifiable information (name and e-mail address) via contact forms of our Services for reaching us about your questions, issues, etc. It’s used only for contact with you to resolve your inquiries.

All other Personal Data we automatically collect through third-party services (“Data Processors”) as a part of our Services. These third-party services may use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, tags, scripts, etc. and collect personal information like IP address, system/browser configuration, network carrier, country/geo location, etc. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these services on an individual or aggregated basis. Here is the list of common third-party services we use in our Services (click on the name of a service for reaching out its Privacy Policy and to know how to opt-out):

a. [Cloudflare](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/) for web optimization and security of our Services

b. [1gb.ru](https://www.1gb.ru/default.aspx?hti=64&ti=6) for hosting online parts of our Services

c. [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for tracking visitors of our Services on anonymous basis

d. [Google Gmail](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for communicating with you

e. [Google Cloud](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for backend of our Services

f. [Google Firebase](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for serving online notifications for you

g. [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/privacy) for personalization of our games and playing with friends. We save and use only your virtual Facebook ID for each Facebook Application

h. [Google DoubleClick](https://policies.google.com/privacy), [AdSense](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [AdMob](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for showing to you personalized and non-personalized advertisement at out Services

i. [CPMStar](https://www.cpmstar.com/privacyPolicy.html) for non-personalized advertisements at our Services

j. [Netlink.vn](https://www.netlink.vn/) for showing to you personalized and non-personalized advertisement at out Services

k. [Harrenmedia](http://harrenmedia.com/?page_id=2203) for showing to you personalized and non-personalized advertisement at out Services

l. [Certified Ad Technology Providers](https://support.google.com/admanager/answer/9012903?hl=en&ref_topic=9007190) for showing to you personalized and non-personalized advertisement at out Services

### 3\. Sharing Personal Information

We don’t sell or rent your Personal Data to others. We enter into a data processing agreement with Data Processors to ensure the same level of security and privacy of your information because they have an access to this information. Also access to Personal Data is restricted only to the employers of Gemioli who require access to this information in order to perform their duties. In other ways we don’t share your information with any other third-party unless for legal reasons.

### 4\. How Long We Store Your Information

We keep your information so long as we need it to provide our Services to you. However, the actual period for which the Personal Data will be stored depends on the circumstances.

### 5\. Children

Our Services don’t intend to collect information from users who are under the age of 16 years. If you are under the age of 16 you must not use our Services for any purpose unless with your parental or legal guardian’s prior consent. Parents may contact us if they have any questions about collecting and processing of their children’s information.

### 6\. Your Rights

We hope we’ve informed you in this Privacy Policy about collection and processing of Personal Data in our Services. You can contact us if you want to review, rectify, erase or restrict processing any of your personal information. We may ask you to identify yourself in order to prevent abuse.

You can set your browser to reject cookies, but some features of our Services will not function normally. You can opt-out of any of used third-party services by reading and doing actions described in their privacy policies.

### 7\. Contacts

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [contact@gemioli.com](mailto:contact@gemioli.com)

### This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 15th 2019.
